export const QuizMarvel = [
    {
        fournisseur: "Donkey Geek (https://www.youtube.com/c/DonkeyGeek)",
        sujet: "Application Marvel Quiz pour apprentissage React JS",
        quizz: {
            debutant: [
                {
                    id: 0,                    id: 0,
                    question: "The React method getDerivedSate FromProps (props, state)is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        "The state of the component is updated",
                        "Both A and B are true.",
                        "None of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "The state of the component is updated",
                    heroId: 1009362
                  },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question: "The componentDidMount method is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        " The component status is updated",
                        "AdamantBoth A and B are true.ium",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "The component is created for the first time",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question: "Which of the following APIs is a must for every ReactJS component?",
                    options: [
                        "getInitialState",
                        " render",
                        "renderComponent",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "renderComponent",
                    heroId: 1009610
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question: "What function can you use to change the state of a React component? ",
                    options: [
                        " this.State = {}",
                        "this.setState",
                        "this.changeState",
                        "Neither of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "this.setState",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question: "Which port is the default port where the webpack-dev-server will run? ",
                    options: [
                        "3000",
                        "8080",
                        "3306",
                        "8000"
                    ],
                    answer: "3000",
                    heroId: 1009664
                },
            ],
            "confirme": [
                {
                    id: 0,                    id: 0,
                    question: "The React method getDerivedSate FromProps (props, state)is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        "The state of the component is updated",
                        "Both A and B are true.",
                        "None of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "The state of the component is updated",
                    heroId: 1009362
                  },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question: "The componentDidMount method is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        " The component status is updated",
                        "AdamantBoth A and B are true.ium",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "The component is created for the first time",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question: "Which of the following APIs is a must for every ReactJS component?",
                    options: [
                        "getInitialState",
                        " render",
                        "renderComponent",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "renderComponent",
                    heroId: 1009610
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question: "What function can you use to change the state of a React component? ",
                    options: [
                        " this.State = {}",
                        "this.setState",
                        "this.changeState",
                        "Neither of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "this.setState",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question: "Which port is the default port where the webpack-dev-server will run? ",
                    options: [
                        "3000",
                        "8080",
                        "3306",
                        "8000"
                    ],
                    answer: "3000",
                    heroId: 1009664
                },
            ],
            "expert": [
                {
                    id: 0,                    id: 0,
                    question: "The React method getDerivedSate FromProps (props, state)is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        "The state of the component is updated",
                        "Both A and B are true.",
                        "None of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "The state of the component is updated",
                    heroId: 1009362
                  },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question: "The componentDidMount method is called when ____?",
                    options: [
                        "The component is created for the first time",
                        " The component status is updated",
                        "AdamantBoth A and B are true.ium",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "The component is created for the first time",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question: "Which of the following APIs is a must for every ReactJS component?",
                    options: [
                        "getInitialState",
                        " render",
                        "renderComponent",
                        "None of the above is true."
                    ],
                    answer: "renderComponent",
                    heroId: 1009610
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question: "What function can you use to change the state of a React component? ",
                    options: [
                        " this.State = {}",
                        "this.setState",
                        "this.changeState",
                        "Neither of the above is true"
                    ],
                    answer: "this.setState",
                    heroId: 1009718
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question: "Which port is the default port where the webpack-dev-server will run? ",
                    options: [
                        "3000",
                        "8080",
                        "3306",
                        "8000"
                    ],
                    answer: "3000",
                    heroId: 1009664
                }
            
            ]
        }
    }
];
